and in some cases I can see that they're
maybe reacting with a thumbs down
because they didn't get the answer that
they wanted the answer was still
accurate and correct but they were like
oh I don't like the fact that you don't
have this feature yet in the product I'm
like that's not a b problem that's a
that's like a a product management
problem you're listening to the AI
native Dev brought to you by Tesla
[Music]
on today's episode we have Amara Graham
from kunda joining us again and this
time around we're going to go into a
screen share covering a lot of the
topics and and and things that we
described in our last podcast Amara is
the uh head of developer experience at
kunda welcome back how are you doing I'm
doing great thank you awesome awesome so
we're going to see uh a little bit
around Kappa which is the AI agent that
you are currently using to take
questions in from your users and work
out what the answers should be with
citations back to the documentation uh
that you have at kunda we're going to go
ahead and share your screen uh now there
we go and you're going to take us
through a few things including various
conversations some dashboards some
analytics as well so why don't you take
us through a brief overview of Kappa
yeah absolutely so Kappa was the the
tool that we chose I'm not here to do a
sales pitch I can't tell you is it the
best is the greatest it's the one that
we're using it's the one that when we
were doing our evaluation made the most
sense for us so this dashboard just
looking at the last month I will say we
are getting super close to our product
release and when we see those minor
releases we tend to get a lot of
traction I guess I'll say so we have a
lot more people coming to our
documentation we potentially have a lot
more people using the AI agent so all
this to say I can't say this is like the
best month we've ever had but it might
be a little bit more um turbulent I
guess I'll say than than other months so
yeah we're looking at the dashboard here
and you can see kind of all of the basic
things that you're looking for the total
questions uncertainty which we talked
about a bit you're able to see a
definition for what uncertainty is
so when Kappa says I'm not sure how to
answer this question it on this back end
logs a little flag so for me or other
folks on my team we're able to come in
and see what does it mean when it's
saying it's uncertain can we improve
this answer like you see it mentioning
in this tool tip all of those things
that kind of roll into the regular
maintenance that we have of Kappa with
that too we also have this concept of
reactions uh you can probably do the
math yourself here and see that we don't
get a lot of Engagement as far as the
reactions are concerned which I always
find very interesting because people are
usually pretty receptive to giving
feedback I guess people are probably far
more likely to downvote something than
out vote something because as soon as
you get something that you want you
click on it you go somewhere else as
soon as there's something that's
annoying you you're far more aota to
actually go no I want to downvote this
because it's annoyed me when we launched
this kind of as a pilot even really just
for internal users I was expecting a lot
more of this kind of Engagement and we
just didn't get it and I think you're on
to something there where it's people are
either getting what they need or they
don't and in some cases I can see that
they're maybe reacting with a thumbs
down because they didn't get the answer
that they wanted the answer was still
accurate and correct but they were like
oh I don't the fact that you don't have
this feature yet in the product I'm like
that's not a b problem that's like a
product management problem but we can
funnel those to the right people to
answer them the unique users thing I
really pay much attention to because of
people have all sorts of things around I
don't want to be tracked we are still
largely a German company so there's
things that we allow people to opt out
of so it's not something that I really
monitor all that much and then this is
relatively new in the sense that it was
not there when we first launched with
Kappa but it's this idea of how are we
improving support or how are we
potentially taking some of that burden
away away from our traditional support
team which is staffed by humans so I
think this is a cool metric to look at
every once in a while but not something
that I moniter the uncertain when the
llm comes back with I can't find an
answer to this I can't find a page on
this is that a metric that you track as
in trying to reduce that month on month
the way to do that is that through
fixing other documentation creating new
documentation or is there like
potentially like product messaging or
something that needs to be fixed what
what what are the resolutions to that I
guess that's a a great question we give
you the standard devil answer it dep it
depends it depends so I actually down
here in in this little chart we get um a
view of the the response certainty and
internally what I've said is I am not
going to take like a deep dive into the
the certain or uncertain questions until
we hit a certain threshold that
threshold for me today right now is if
it's above 10% okay I will say that 7%
here is pretty high our documentation
like guess not to toot my own horn our
documentation is typically so good that
it's getting closer to a 3% uncertain
response week over week so occasionally
again we're heading towards our minor
release that's in October so we do see a
bit more traffic we do see people start
to ask questions about what features are
coming I don't expect expect Kappa to
answer those questions because the the
information is just not there but I set
a threshold for myself to say at 10%
we'll take action usually we're hovering
somewhere around the 3 four five% range
so I can't be too bothered about that
that said I do dig into I just have
another tab open here the uncertain
tagged questions and click into them and
say okay can I get a just very basic
triage of what's going on here was
question worded strange is it something
that I know is potentially coming in a
future release like I mentioned with
this minor release that's coming up and
then we have these tools on the back end
to be able to say do I want to improve
this answer directly here and then feed
that back into kappa's training data or
do I need to say this is actually
something that needs to be fixed in the
documentation let's go ahead and and do
that with a a pull request or depending
on on the severity or what we need to
change do we need to launch like an
official project so there's several
things that are going on behind the
scenes with that but again I'm coming in
here monthly and taking a look at things
just to make sure acting as I would
expect it to but I do know there's some
seasonality here where I say 10% is my
threshold for action but we're typically
hovering around 5% seven seems a bit
high but knowing that we have this
upcoming minor release again I'm not
really moved to action but I'll still go
through and and have a look at some of
those conversations see what people are
asking where it's getting flagged as
uncertain and then potentially take
action on those one-off situations
interesting I I really love the fact
that you can actually make a change to
the training data and presumably that's
just updating some rag somewhere that
kind of allows it to have that
additional data yeah so I I'll quickly
show the the sources here and and how we
have them configured some of the sources
we have to go through and pull them
manually you can see last ingested dates
some of this data doesn't really change
all of that much I can go through and
manually ingest some data some of it
gets pulled and ingested automatically
but yeah there's a couple of different
things that we can do if we see the
answers aren't quite right or we know
that was something was updated recently
where do we want to make that change is
it a change to the in ingested data so
we need to pull from Source or is is it
something that we need to change one off
we have the option to do either how much
change is there in terms of adding new
sources is there much that gets done on
a kind of like weekly basis or is it
largely uh similar over time again
because we have this kind of like
seasonality as we're working towards
releases we do monthly Alpha releases
and then two or three times a year we do
minor releases those minor releases are
quite large typically and so what will
happen is as we get closer to that Miner
I will make sure that we have the
freshest data possible and again this is
running in this like refresh State
depending on what source we're pulling
from what's getting ingested but I
always make sure that when we do a very
significant docs release that we make
sure we pull in the the documentation um
so that it's the the fresh as possible
so maybe that's happening monthly maybe
that's happening a couple times monthly
but we do have a Cron job that basically
runs and fetches this and then I can go
through and review do I really need to
add that is there significant changes
there can take care of that and know
there's an Integrations piece there as
well how would you integrate kaer into
your into your workflow things like
slack Integrations as well and things
like that or is it mostly yes with you
are yeah so we can do slack Integrations
you'll see maybe if you have really Keen
eyes because I didn't quite point it out
that we have other teams or other areas
that are using Kappa so we have our
communic Academy team discourse is our
community Forum so depending on what
they are looking for from a tool like
Kappa they can do some amount of
integration for us in the documentation
space we maintain such a large and
significant part of the source data that
for us our source of truth if you will
is always going to be the documentation
so if people have problems with the docs
they're either internally letting us
know on respective slack channels or our
docs are open source and public so
people can create issues create PLL
requests and we're handling more of it
there this is really a check on the the
accuracy and completeness very similar
to if we were doing I don't know a
traditional review so you're going in
and seeing docs for a new feature is it
complete does it make sense do we think
our customers will be able to respond to
it in that sense Kappa or this Kappa
ecos system is contributing to that and
is a I don't know a power user in that
sense because it's able to collect all
of this feedback on all these various
topics and then it's on us to say do we
need to take action and modify that is
it something that is just a product Gap
is that something that we would then
address with a change to the docs or not
or is that something that we just ignore
so there's a little bit more gardening
I'll say going on in the the back end
where it's
do we need to take action on that now or
as things naturally roll out the the
life cycle of the product continues this
will shake out and um it's not something
that we need to address immediately and
actually one final question uh you
mentioned in the last podcast episode
about the fact that you have search as
well as the kind of the chat UI uh
available and people can use either how
do you see the numbers here effectively
being resolved through a chat UI versus
a user potenti entially getting the
results from a search passing in
keywords from a usual search box do you
see the success rate being higher for
one versus the other yeah so that's a
very interesting question and I don't
have a good view of it because we have
two ways to search one is through the
Kappa AI tool itself where ask AI is
going to be that back and forth dialogue
if you want you can ask more a human
oriented question or you can just do a a
regular search here we see both of those
things happening and I think like I was
mentioning we'll see people use the aski
part with keywords as well so they're
using it as a search box we also have a
search box that's just built in that's
powered by algolia I think this is
something that our docs framework runs
on docusaurus I think algolia partnered
very early on with docusaurus to make it
available for open- Source projects and
there is a little bit then of kind of
triage that I'm doing where I'm watching
both spaces to see do we have anything
that's maybe trending in one place or
the other is there any issues with our
users getting the information that they
need in a successful way or an efficient
way and trying to then understand what
do we need to do what actions do we need
to take again that comes down to is our
documentation formatted correctly isn't
a way that machines and humans can parse
some of that comes up with how people
people are searching the terms that
people are using and then all of this
gets baked into how we want to to
structure our docs pages so what you
can't see is some of the metadata behind
the scenes for these Pages include
additional keywords so that we're
flagging to search engines to the AI
agent that this is something that's
relevant that gets us back into the
traditional SEO side of things yeah
which again is why I say like machine
learning deep learning was like the
early segue into these AI agents and how
people interact with them and this
concept of data ingestion all this has
been around for quite a long time and so
we say for our docs if we are following
SEO best practices we should be able to
also do really well with these AI agents
and getting them you know the right
information structured in the right way
that they find it as well yeah bitting
your future hat on DC yourselves
potentially looking at switching
entirely over to just ask AI at some
stage yeah that's such a great question
because again I come back to watching
some of the user behavior in here and I
don't have to click into these for you
to be able to see this little number
sign this is how many kind of
interactions or back and forth people
are are having I'm sure Kappa has a
better definition than that but that's
what I'm going to call it and you can
see that many of these things are these
oneoff what is dmn they're just looking
for a basic definition maybe they're
going into viewing this link and they're
quite happy with that and bouncing so I
look at this and say based on our
current user Behavior I think if the ask
AI agent is responding well to these one
off either questions or things like just
a a statement or a keyword then I think
I'll just leave it as is but again it
comes back to if you're evaluating any
of these similar tools it depends on
your user base if your user base is
totally comfortable asking like fully
wellth thought out questions and they're
getting what they need then I would say
that search is not really keyword search
I guess I should say is not something
they're going to use that's fine but for
something like Kappa it seems to do both
pretty well so if people want to just
shout terms at it it's G to respond if
people want to give it good questions
it's gonna respond and in that case I'm
like cool business as usual just depends
on how chatty people want to be it
exactly and I didn't pull up before we
started it a good example but we have
some people that get very chatty with it
and I'm just like oh okay this is great
and maybe that also says something about
like how we're seeing the evolution of
paired programming with some of these
tools and as people get more comfortable
with co-pilot tools and things that
they're able to interrogate as they
write code or draft documentation that
we might see behavioral changes but yeah
early on when we first implemented it I
was like I'm glad this is a a robot
because people just shout things at it
like G give me this parameter thing but
instead of saying even that they're just
like parameter name yeah keyword this
I'm like a it has no feelings it's
probably good awesome Mara I really
appreciate you sharing this and thank
you for the under the cover's view of
what Kappa looks like from the
dashboards and from the conversations
point of view yeah and I think you
mentioned at the end of the last episode
that you very much recommended people
try this out I think you're having you
know good success with it in within your
uh developer experience yeah absolutely
and I say it's not a sales pitch I know
there's a number of of vendors out there
what I always tell people who are in
like the the management or leadership
position for choosing these tools is
make sure it works for you your team
your community so maybe you have a
community that's a lot more receptive to
uncertainty and you want it to do some
amount of hallucination because you want
to get that as I don't know user
feedback and validation go for it for
our us though I know I went very
structured lots of guidelines and guard
rails because I know the tolerance for
hallucinations for our community is
quite low so again it's just a matter of
knowing your community knowing your
users and then my biggest thing that I
want to tell people is don't just turn
it on and ignore it make sure that
you're monitoring it set thresholds like
I mentioned to say we need to take
action or a deep investigation at a
certain uncertainty threshold but it's a
really great tool and it's great for
user validation it's great for
validating things like our docs working
correctly because that's a hard question
to answer and this is a a a great tool
and a great way to have that answer
thank you very much for not just one but
a couple of parts to this episode we
appreciate you joining us and and thank
you for sharing all that very useful
information yeah thank you so much and
thanks all for listening and hope you
tune in to the next session
[Music]
thanks for tuning in join us next time
on the AI native Dev brought to you by
chass